그래! 잠깐
거기엔 너도 포함되지?
많이 좋아하나 봐?
상상도 못할 거야
함께 무대에 서면 키스하고 안고 싶어져
감독과 집에 가는 모습을 보고 있으면
내 맘이 찢어진다구
그런 심정을 안다니 정말 잘됐어
- 안녕 - 어서 와
아버지 전화를 받았는데...
실비아 이모가 돌아가셨대
정말! 정말! 좋다!
다들 흥분에 떨고 있어
뭔가 잘못된 거 아냐? 죽음이란 건 슬픈 일이잖아
실비아 이모가 그리 좋은 분이 아니었어
냉정하고, 괴팍한 분이었지
돌아가신 건 안 됐어
- 아빠가 인형 집은 보내셨대? - 곧 도착한대
나도 인형 집을 갖는다!
인형이 살 집? 멋지다
난 어릴 적에, 통이 있었어
인형을 통에 넣었어?
그냥 통만 있었어
인형 집이 오면 우리 같이 놀아
정말? 정말?
언제든지
어릴 적 소원이 인형 집을 갖는 거였어
물론, 지금은 감상용이지 갖고 놀 생각은 없어
우리 할머니도 똑같은 말씀을 하셨지
- 나 왔어, 소피 - 왔어
안녕하세요?
점심 잘 먹었어
여기까지 바래다 줄 필요는 없는데
괜찮아, 그냥 온 거야
사무실에 여자 란제리를 걸어놓진 않아
응, 지금 봤어
- 여름 카탈로그야 - 바로 이거야
베르사체 송장이 어딨지?
안녕하세요? 직원은 아니시죠?
과장님 제 친구 챈들러 빙이에요
조애너 과장님
빙? 재밌는 이름이군요
게일족 말로 '너의 칠면조가 다 됐다'래요
이제 갈게요 반가웠습니다
- 저두요 - 잘 가, 챈들러
사람이 원래 저래?
원래 좀 맹해 보이지만 저는 이제 거의 모르겠어요
아니, 좋단 뜻이야
혹시 기혼자거나 애인이 있나?
아뇨, 미혼이고 애인도 없어요
레이첼... 있잖아 아냐, 됐어
- 원하시면 제가 물어볼게요 - 그럴래?
그래도 너무 몸 달은 것처럼 하지마, 소피처럼 말이야
저 여기 있어요
알아
이것 봐!
벽지가 좀 어둡지만... 괜찮아
카페트가 좀 낡았네
바닥이 나무야!
- 안녕 - 왔니?
모니카! 너무 아름답다
그래!
- 내가 준비해왔어 - 좋아
이 집을 위해서 준비했어 어디 보자
이게 뭐야?
개야, 집마다 개가 있잖아
지붕에다 오줌싸라구?
방사성 폐기물 위에 세워진 집이라 변종이 된 거야
집이 재채기도 하니?
아냐, 그건 다락방의 유령이야
난 유령 싫어
유령은 누구나 싫어해
그래도 이 집엔 있어
이 집이 고대 인디안 묘지 자리에 지어졌거든
이 집이 방사성 폐기물과 고대 인디안 묘지에 있는 거야?
그건 말도 안 돼
넌 미국 정부가 어떤지 몰라
- 안녕 - 안녕
우리 얘기 좀 해
그래, 뭔데?
미안, 챈들러에게 한 말이야
알고 있어
그래도 혹시나...
너희가 덜 어색한 단계로 접어든 걸 축하해
조애너 과장 알지?
네가 나가자마자 너에 대해서 묻더라
잠깐 본 건데?
내 행동은 어떻대?
챈챈맨의 위력을 보시라!
너무...
초현실적이다
어때? 관심 있니?
응, 괜찮아 보이더라 매력도 있고, 나야 좋지
고마워, 잘됐다 과장님한테 잘 보일 거야
공룡의 공격이다! 모두 집안으로 들어가!
피비, 됐어 그만 하자
공룡도, 유령도 거인 개도 됐어
크기도 안 맞고, 빅토리아풍과 안 어울려
알았어, 됐어
가자, 공룡아
상상력이 없는 집은 우리도 필요 없어
피비, 전문가 입장에서 말하는 건데....
공룡과는 손 붙잡고 가지마
작은 건 괜찮아
- 케이트 - 좋은 아침!
지난주에 말해준 그 식당에 갔었어요
귀염둥이! 이리 와요 얘기 좀 합시다
식사했죠, 맛있었어요 생선요리였죠, 좋았어요
안녕하세요
로렌이에요 케이트 보조 대역이죠
조이 트리비아니예요
알아요, 당신 팬이에요
네?
라모레이 박사를 보느라고 수업 시간도 바꾸고 그랬죠
'우리의 날들'이요
- 정말이에요? - 물론이죠
그런데 엘리베이터에 끼어 죽게 한 건 너무했어요
아주 설득력 있는 죽음이죠
어머, 너무 재밌네요
리허설 끝나고 뭐 하세요? 술이라도 한잔 하실래요?
그게...
좋아요, 술 한잔 좋죠
좋아요
- 그럼 있다 봬요 - 그래요
이제 연기를 해봅시다
한번 떠들어봐요!
- 안녕 - 안녕
이것 봐라 내 인형 집이야
봐, 봐!
이게 뭐야?
미끄럼 계단이야, 봐
아주 재밌다, 피비
이건 뭐야?
약초 방이야 먹을 수 있는 가구지
손님이 오면 접는 침대를 펴면 돼
지금까지 본 것 중에 최고다!
아로마 방에 가고 싶은 사람?
- 저요 - 저요
여길 봐, 내 장식장 봤어?
이거 봐!
이것도!
우리 아빠 집도 저랬어
좋아! 어땠는지 말해봐
영화 좋았고, 식사 좋았고 쌀쌀한 뉴욕의 밤 분위기 좋고!
근데 난 그걸 즐길 수 없었어 조애너 같은 여자는 처음이다
챈들러, 너무 좋아!
네?
우린 천생연분이야 그게 어떤지 알지?
그가 날 데리러 옴과 동시에 내가 문을 열었어
- 그런 말 안 해? - 저는...
게다가 너무 착해 정말 착하지 않아?
- 저는... - 그래, 너무 좋은 사람이야
전화한다고 했으니까 바로 바꿔 줘
- 정말 잘 됐네요 - 기분 깨지마
여보, 제발 가지마 안 떠날 거지?
여보세요? 당신이군 잠깐만
전화를 받고 올테니까
그때는 이 극장 무대에 매혹적인 게 보이길 바래요
순간에 전념해요!
괴상하지 않아요?
당신은 못 느껴요?
좋을 때도 있잖아요
당신이 데이트하는 저 스웨터 보단 낫죠
난 스웨터엔 관심 없어요
스웨터 속이 중요하죠
언제부터 남의 데이트 상대에 신경을 썼죠?
난 신경 안 써요 신경 써주길 원해요?
신경 써주길 원하길 원해요?
당신은요?
뭐요?
이렇게 말하긴 두렵지만, 하던 거 계속합시다
여보, 제발 가지마 안 떠날 거지?
있어야 할 이유가 없어요
그만! 그만해! 제발 그만해!
당신들 연기는 끔찍스러워
각본도 끔찍해!
내일 아침에 봅시다
1주일 밖에 안 남았어요
할 수 있을 거예요
오늘 일찍 끝났으니까 머그컵 색칠하러 갈래요?
네?
어제 말씀 드린 곳이요
그래요, 컵에 색칠하는 곳이요
아주 잘 기억하죠?
근데 오늘은 남아서 연습해야겠어요
알았어요 내일 만나요
그래요
먼저 갈게요
괜찮아요?
네, 괜찮아요
이 장면을 어떻게 하죠?
모르겠어요
좀 더 극적인 게 필요해요
어쩌면 되죠?
아내는 남을 이유를 찾고 싶어하죠
남편은 키스도 못해요
그는 아내에게 이유를 찾아줘야 돼요
찐한 키스는 어떨까요?
아니면... 여자를 잡고
번쩍 들어올려요
좋아요, 그럼 아내가 다리로 남편의 허리를 감죠
남편의 옷을 찢고 그의 가슴에 입을 맞추죠
남편은 입으로 아내의 드레스를 벗겨요
그리고 콱 깨물죠!
네, 결국... 거칠고 동물적인...
이렇게요?
내 생각과 거의 비슷해요
네
- 왔냐? - 안녕
아침부터 술 마셨니?
아니 결국 케이트와 일을 냈다
- 정말? 잘 됐다 - 그래
너무 놀라웠어 사랑을 나눈 뒤에...
세상에
몇 시간 동안 자는 모습을 지켜봤어
숨을 들이쉬고, 내쉬고...
꿈을 꾸고 있었나봐 눈이 이렇게 움직였거든
조애너와 안 맞아 내가 한 말이라곤...
"재밌네요, 또 옵시다 전화할게요"
이런! 그래서 전화 올 거라는 말을 했구나?
데이트 끝엔 누구나 하잖아
반가웠어요, 잘 가요 그랬어야지
그 얼굴에 대고?
헤어질 때쯤, 뭔가를 기다리는 듯한 분위기에
'전화할게요'가 저절로 튀어나오더라
어쩔 수 없었어 강박을 느낄 정도였어
남자가 전화한단 말이 꼭 한다는 건 아니잖아
넌 그런 적 없어?
난 늘 받았어
잘났어
전화 왔어?
아뇨, 죄송해요
왜? 한다고 해놓고 왜 전화를 안 하는 거야?
똑똑하고, 강하고, 성공한 여자 기피증이 있나봐요
소피, 말참견 좀 하지 마
- 전화를 왜 안 한 대? - 그게, 아마도...
제 상관이라는 게 부담스러웠나봐요
- 부담? 무슨 부담을 느껴? - 그게...
부담스러운 건 레이첼 아냐? 그래서 전화하지 말랬지?
아뇨!
직장 상사와 친구의 데이트가 불편하면 방법을 찾아봐야지
전화해, 당장!
한 마리 매처럼 채가네
왜 전화 안 하지? 왜? 왜?
이해할 수 없어, 왜? 한다고 했는데, 왜지?
과장이 잔뜩 골이 나있어! 화가 났다구!
- 그럼 전화기 줘 - 지금 웃을 기분 아냐
과장은 내 책임이라고 생각하니까, 빨리 해
막무가내로 부탁 아닌 명령을 하는 사람의 말을 들으라구?
아님, 같이 외출이라도 해
싫어! 정말 지루한 여자야
속눈썹에 마스카라 덩어리도 묻히고 다녀
상관없어! 상관없어!
한번 더 데이트하고서 진짜 확실하게 끝내버려
아무리 어쩔 수 없다해도 절대로 전화한단 말 하지마
좋아, 알았어
이번은 점심 데이트야 1시간 이상은 못해
이제 내 짝은 내가 찾아 절대로 여자 소개하지마
그거 좋지!
- 우리 소리 좀 크지 않니? - 알아
모니카?
샤워 중이야
불이야! 불이야!
- 안녕 - 안녕
로렌과 얘길 했는데, 우리 사이를 밝혔어요
당신은 감독한테 말했어요?
무슨 얘기요?
지난 밤 얘기요
아뇨
그 사람이 알아야 할 이유가 없어요
별 일 아니었잖아요
그게 무슨 뜻이죠? 그건 별 일이에요
지난밤 일이 별 거 아니란 말은 말아요
분명 일어난 일이고, 당신도 그리 훌륭한 배우는 아니죠
그건... 순간적으로 일어난 거였어요
그뿐이에요
기분 나빴다면 미안해요
자고 나서, 그것의 의미가 다른 적도 있지 않아요?
아뇨
- 안녕, 케이트 - 안녕, 로렌
안녕, 로렌
나쁜 놈!
- 놀래켜서 미안해 - 괜찮아
아무튼, 난 샤워기를 손보고 있었어
알아
안녕
직장에 전화했었어 집에 불이 났어
뭐? 어머... 맙소사!
어떻게 된 거야?
화재가 발생한 곳은 여깁니다
아로마 룸이죠
대피는 잘 했어?
기린은 괜찮고, 해적도 괜찮아
이게 뭐니?
피비, 안돼 그거 안 보는 게 나을걸!
입양한 인형인데!
괜찮아요, 그냥 보여서요 자꾸 보이거든요
점심 잘 먹었어요
저도 즐거웠습니다
그렇죠?
- 음식도 맛있었죠 - 그렇죠?
그럼, 잘 있어요
당신도요
즐거웠고, 전화 드리죠 언제 또 봅시다
좋아요, 기다리죠
- 레이첼, 전화 메모는? - 소피 책상에요
챈들러! 전화할 거야?
- 아니 - 챈들러?
미안해, 나약하고 덜 떨어져서 미안해
솔직히 말해, 지금 하라구
저... 전화 안할래요
네?
죄송해요
생각도 없이 한다고 해서 죄송해요
당신이 문제가 있어서가 아니고, 레이첼 잘못도 아니죠
제가 여자에 있어서 심각한 문제가 있어요
책임감이나 친밀감에 문제가 있고...
마스카라 덩어리도요
정말 죄송하지만 계속 만날 수가 없어요
이런 식으로 끝나는 건 싫지만 솔직하게 말해주니 고맙군요
네... 그래요
그럼...
즐거웠고, 전화 드리죠 언제 또 봅시다
어쨌든, 베스
너희 집에 갔을 때 네 기분을 몰랐단 거야
내가 요즘 여자들 입장이 돼보는 중이거든, 미안해
날 용서할 수 있겠어?
그래, 고마워 그럼 잘 있어
제니퍼?
로리오 부인! 제니퍼 있어요?
나갔군요?
사실, 부인께도 드릴 말씀이 있어요
You're telling me this actress person...
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
Oh, my God.
Is this what it's like to be you?
-You're crazy about her, huh? -You have no idea.
When we're on stage, I get to kiss her and touch her.
She goes home with the director...
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
Oh, it's so great to see you feeling like this.
Dad called this morning.
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
Am I missing something?
I thought death was supposed to be sad, in a way.
Well, Aunt Sylvia was...
... not a nice person.
She was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
And I'm sorry she died.
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
-You get the dollhouse. -I get the dollhouse!
A house for dolls! That is so cool.
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
No, just a barrel.
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
Really?
Any time you want.
When I was young I wanted to play with this dollhouse.
But no! It was to be looked at, never played with.
My grandmother said the same thing to me.
The One With the Doll House
Thanks for lunch. You didn't have to walk me here.
That's okay. No problem.
You realize we don't keep the women's lingerie here.
Yes, I realize that.
-Summer catalog. -That's the stuff.
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
You don't work for me.
Joanna, this is my friend Chandler Bing. Joanna.
Bing? That's a great name.
It's Gaelic for, "Thy turkey's done."
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you. -You too.
So what's wrong with him?
Nothing. He's just goofy like that. I actually hardly notice it anymore.
I mean, is he married or involved with anyone?
He's not married or involved with anyone.
Actually, you know what? Forget it.
-I'll ask him for you, if you want. -Would you?
Or is it too sad and desperate, like something Sophie would do?
-I am here. -I know that.
Look at it!
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
Carpet's a little loose.
Hardwood floors?!
-It's so beautiful! -I know!
So I'm here, ready to play!
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house, so check it out.
What's this?
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
Not one that can pee on the roof.
Maybe it's so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.
And is this in case the house sneezes?
No, that's the ghost for the attic.
-I don't want a ghost. -Well, nobody wants a ghost.
But you've got one...
... because the house is sitting on an ancient lndian burial ground.
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
...and an ancient lndian burial ground?
That would never happen.
Obviously you don't know much about the U.S. government.
-I need to talk to you. -Sure. What's up?
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
I know.
Well, if something comes up....
I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
...she started asking questions about you....
Liked what she saw?
Dug my action, did she?
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
That was...
...surreal.
What do you think? Are you interested?
She seemed cool. Attractive. I'll do it.
Thank you, Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
Dinosaur attack! Quick, everybody into the house!
All right, Phoebe, you know what? That's it. That's it.
No dinosaurs, no ghosts, no giant dogs, okay?
They're not the right size, they're not Victorian and they don't go.
Fine.
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
While we're on the subject, I have to say that dinosaurs...
...they don't go, "ruff!"
The little ones do.
-Hey, Kate. -Morning.
I went to that restaurant you talked about
Hey, lovely.
Come, talk to me for a minute.
I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
Joey Tribbiani.
I know.
I'm a big fan of yours.
What?
I used to schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...on Days of our Lives.
-Get out of here. Really? -Absolutely.
But then they dropped you down that elevator shaft.
They gave me the shaft, all right.
You're so funny.
What are you doing after rehearsal?
You want to get a drink?
Sure. A drink sounds great.
-Cool. I'll see you then. -All right.
All right. It's time to act, my talking props.
Look everybody! Look at my new dollhouse!
Look, look!
Hey, what's this?
It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
Very interesting, Phoebe.
What's this?
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
And when guests come over, they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
This is the coolest house ever!
Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
-All right. -I would.
Hey, guys? Guys!
Did you see my new china cabinet?
Watch. Watch.
And? And?
Hey, my father's house does that.
How did it go? Tell me everything!
The movie was great...
...dinner was great, and there's nothing like a cool, crisp New York evening.
Of course, I didn't enjoy any of that because Joanna's such a dull dud!
Chandler is fantastic!
-What? -You know how people just click?
He came by to pick me up, I opened the door and it was just like, "click!"
Did he tell you?
Doesn't he have a good heart?
And he's so sweet. He said he'd call, so put him straight through.
-lsn't this great? -Don't spoil it.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
It's you. Just one sec.
I'm going to take this call.
When I continue, I hope there will appear on-stage...
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
...committing to the moment!
The guy's like a cartoon.
What do you see in him, anyway?
He happens to be brilliant.
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
I'm not interested in her sweater.
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
And besides...
...since when do you care who I'm with?
I don't care. Why, do you want me to care?
Do you want me to want you to care?
Do you?
What?
Okay. I'm afraid to say this, but let's pick up where we left off.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please? What do you say?
I've got no reason to stay.
Stop!
Stop it! You must stop!
You are bad actors!
This is a terrible play!
I'll see you in the morning.
I can't believe we go on in a week.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
Since we're getting off early, do you want to go paint mugs?
What?
At the place I told you about last night?
Yeah, with the mug-painting.
I was so listening to that.
But you know what? I need to work on my stuff tonight.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Are you okay?
I guess.
What are we gonna do about the scene?
I don't know.
Maybe if it had more heat.
Well, how do you mean?
Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay, right?
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
... he's gotta give her a reason.
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
Or maybe...
... maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs around his waist.
Then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest and stomach.
Then he could use his teeth to undo her dress and...
...and bite her!
Then right when the scene ends, he could take her...
...with this raw, animal....
Something like that?
That's pretty much what I had in mind.
It's a little early to be drinking.
Things finally happened with Kate.
You're kidding? That's great.
It was so amazing.
After the lovemaking...
Oh, my.
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
Just breathing in...
...and breathing out.
I knew she was dreaming because...
... her eyes kept going like this.
I'm telling you, she's got it all wrong.
All I said was, "This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
I'll give you a call."
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
It's what you say at the end of a date.
You can't just say, "Nice to meet you. Good night?"
To her face?
I'm standing there...
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
...and it comes out. I can't help it.
It's a compulsion.
When a guy says he'll call, it doesn't mean he's going to call.
This never happened to you?
Well, they always called.
Bite me.
-Did he call? -No, sorry.
Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
Maybe he's intimidated by smart, strong, successful women.
Sophie, will you please climb out of my butt.
Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why?
Maybe he feels awkward because you're my boss.
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
You didn't tell him not to call me, did you?
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating me...
...there are always ways to fix that.
Call her. Call her now!
Multiple so many paper cuts.
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why, why? I don't understand!"
I'm telling you, she's flipped out! She's gone crazy!
Well, give me the phone then.
She thinks it's my fault you haven't called her.
You have to call her.
You can't call somebody after this long to say:
"In case you didn't notice, I don't like you."
Then you'll have to take her out again.
She's really dull, and she gets this...
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye!
I don't care!
You'll take her out again and end it...
...in a way she knows it's ended.
I don't care how hard it is. Don't tell her you'll call her again!
All right, fine!
But just lunch. From now on, I get my own dates.
I don't want you setting me up again!
That's fine!
-That's just a lot of big talk. -I know.
I'm in the shower!
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
I talked to Lauren. I told her how things were with us.
Did you talk to Marshall?
About what?
About what happened with us.
No, there's really no reason why he should find out.
So let's not make a big deal out of it, okay?
What are you talking about?
It was a big deal.
You can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
I was just caught up in the moment.
That's all it was.
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad, but...
... haven't you slept with a woman and it meant more to her than to you?
Hi, pig!
Sorry I scared you in there.
It's okay.
By the way...
... I was just checking the shower massager.
I tried to reach you at work.
There's been a fire.
What? Oh, my God!
What happened?
We believe it originated here...
...in the Aroma Room.
Did everyone get out okay?
The giraffe's okay, and so is the pirate.
-What's this? -No, don't look!
You don't want to see what's under there!
The foster puppets!
It's not a big deal. It's right here, and it's all the time.
Thanks again for lunch.
-This was pleasant. -lt was, wasn't it?
-The food there was great. -Wasn't it?
So take care.
You too.
I'll give you a call. We should do it again!
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
-Any messages? -Sophie's desk.
Are you gonna call her?
I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
You are gonna tell her. You'll tell her now.
I'm not gonna call you.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I said I was going to when I'm not.
This has nothing to do with you.
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
I have serious problems when it comes to women.
I have issues with commitment, intimacy...
... mascara goop.
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
...this isn't going to work out.
This isn't how I was hoping this would end...
... but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime!
Anyway, Beth, what I'm saying is...
... I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you.
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side...
...and I'm sorry.
Do you think you can forgive me?
Great. Thanks.
Hello, Jennifer?
Hi, Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
She's not home, huh?
Actually I kind of need to talk to you too.